{
    "subject": "Henri-Georges_Clouzot",
    "predicate": "created",
    "object": "La_V\u00e9rit\u00e9__film_",
    "human_readable": "Henri-Georges Clouzot created the film La V\u00e9rit\u00e9.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9073285460472107,
            "question": "Who created the film La V\u00e9rit\u00e9?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8996566534042358,
            "question": "Who was Henri-Georges Clouzot?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8862479329109192,
            "question": "What is the title of the film directed by Henri-Georges Clouzot?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8556970953941345,
            "question": "What other films did Henri-Georges Clouzot create?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7301375865936279,
            "question": "What are some common themes explored in films directed by Henri-Georges Clouzot?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7158700227737427,
            "question": "Is La V\u00e9rit\u00e9 a film?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5701697468757629,
            "question": "Can you name another famous French filmmaker from a similar era as Henri-Georges Clouzot?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.45456066727638245,
            "question": "Where might you find information about the plot of La V\u00e9rit\u00e9?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3359626829624176,
            "question": "When was La V\u00e9rit\u00e9 likely released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.31304073333740234,
            "question": "What genre is La V\u00e9rit\u00e9 likely to be?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Henri-Georges Clouzot created the film La V\u00e9rit\u00e9.",
            "html": "yago_23830_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=When was La V\u00e9rit\u00e9 likely released?",
            "html": "yago_23830_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where might you find information about the plot of La V\u00e9rit\u00e9?",
            "html": "yago_23830_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you name another famous French filmmaker from a similar era as Henri-Georges Clouzot?",
            "html": "yago_23830_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_23830_100.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_23830_112.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_23830_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_23830_132.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_23830_134.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_23830_141.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_23830_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_23830_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_23830_58.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_23830_66.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple in JSON format:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe reason for this answer is that according to the context information, there are multiple documents that mention Henri-Georges Clouzot and his film La V\u00e9rit\u00e9. For example, document /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_23830/re-ranker-msmarco/56.txt mentions \"Clouzot made La V\u00e9rit\u00e9 in 1960...\" and document /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_23830/re-ranker-msmarco/80.txt states \"What emerges is a nuanced portrait of an impulsive young woman misunderstood and mistreated by those around her, and of her ultimately tragic affair with an up-and-coming conductor.  With an astonishing performance by Bardot, Clouzot\u2019s affecting and intricately constructed film\u2014a huge late-career success for the French master\u2014renders a harsh verdict against a hypocritical and moralistic society.\" This information supports the triple that Henri-Georges Clouzot created the film La V\u00e9rit\u00e9."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about Henri-Georges Clouzot and his film \"La V\u00e9rit\u00e9,\" confirming that he was indeed the creator of this film."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}